Now, that we've made some conclusions,
وصلنا الآن إلى بعض الاستنتاجات،
we can create visualizations to display our findings regarding
يمكننا إنشاء مرئيات لعرض نتائجنا فيما يتعلق
the associations between wine quality and different properties of wine.
بالرابطات بين جودة المشروبات والخصائص المختلفة للمشروب.
I've already imported pandas and loaded our edited wine quality data.
لقد قمت باستيراد pandas وحملت بيانات جودة المشروبات المعدلة.
Let's also include the matplotlib inline statement to view plots in our notebook.
دعونا أيضًا ندرج عبارة matplotlib inline لعرض الرسومات في دفتر الملاحظات.
Let's create visualizations, to help us understand if a certain type of wine,
لننشئ مرئيات، لتساعدنا في فهم إذا كان نوع معين من المشروب،
red or white, is associated with higher quality.
سواء أحمر أم أبيض، مرتبط بالجودة العالية.
In the previous section,
في القسم السابق،
we used groupby to find the mean wine quality for each color.
استخدمنا groupby لإيجاد وسط جودة المشروبات لكل لون.
We're going to use these results for these visualizations.
سنستخدم هذه النتائج لهذه المرئيات.
To do this, we can add plot to the end of the groupby statement.
للقيام بذلك، يمكننا إضافة أمر plot في نهاية عبارة groupby.
We can also specify parameters for the title,
يمكننا أيضًا تخصيص معلمات للعنوان،
as well as the color and transparency of the bars.
وكذلك لون وشفافية الشرائط.
Let's actually create a separate list for colors to make this cleaner.
لننشئ قائمة منفصلة للألوان لنجعله أكثر نظافة.
This makes sense, when there are multiple colors you want to graph with multiple times.
هذا أمر منطقي، عندما يكون هناك عدة ألوان تريد أن ترسم بها الرسم البياني عدة مرات.
For our final visualizations,
وبالنسبة للمرئيات النهائية،
we should have appropriate labels for both the x and y axis.
يجب أن يكون لدينا تسميات ملائمة للمحورين X و Y.
We also don't want our white bar disappearing into a white background.
ولا نريد أيضًا أن يختفي شريطنا الأبيض في الخلفية البيضاء.
At this point, we can't get away with using only pandas.
عند هذه النقطة، لا يمكننا الابتعاد باستخدام pandas فقط.
Let's add matplotlib. Pyplot is a module in matplotlib we'll use to create our plots.
دعونا نضيف matplotlib. Pyplot عبارة عن وحدة نمطية في matplotlib سنستخدمها لإنشاء رسومنا.
Standard convention is to import it and alias it as plt.
الاصطلاح القياسي هو استيرادها وتسميتها باسم مستعار مثل plt.
Let's also import seaborn.
لنقم أيضا باستيراد seaborn.
Seaborn standard alias is sns.
الاسم القياسي المستعار لـ seaborn هو sns.
Even if we don't use seaborn directly,
حتى إذا لم نستخدم seaborn مباشرة،
it adds additional formatting to our plots that make them more
فإنها تضيف تنسيقات إضافية على رسومنا
aesthetically pleasing, than standard matplotlib.
لتصبح أكثر إرضاءً من الناحية الجمالية من matplotlib القياسية.
Additional information on this is provided below.
تتوافر معلومات إضافية بشأن هذا أدناه.
Now, that we have matplotlib, we can set x and y axis labels like this.
الآن، بما أننا لدينا matplotlib، يمكننا أن نعين المحورين X و Y هكذا.
Our graph looks nicer and the white part doesn't blend into the background.
يبدو رسمنا البياني على نحوٍ أفضل ولم يندمج الجزء الأبيض مع الخلفية.
Although this works, that first line of code is pretty long and difficult to read.
رغم نجاح هذا، إلا أن السطر الأول من الكود طويل للغاية ويصعب قراءته.
Let's assign the groupby statement to a new object.
لنعين عبارة groupby لكائن جديد.
This won't change the visualization itself,
لن يغير ذلك المرئيات نفسها،
It just makes our lives easier.
ولكن يجعل الموضوع أسهل.